A Guide to the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records FA1420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1955-1983; 1; 58.87 Cubic Feet 155 letter-size document boxes. Boxes 1-155.
  - R-S-T-U-V
    - Schoenbohm, William Siegfried (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Schola Cantorum (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Schonbrun, Sheila (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Schotten-Collier Duo (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Schrade, Robert (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Schramm, Adelaida (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Schreiner, Christine (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Schroeder, Peter (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Schumacher, Thomas (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Schubert, Hazel (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Schuessler, Merrily (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - Schuh, Audrey (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - Schultz, Carl (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - Schuster, Margaret (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - Schuster, Milton (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Schwarzschild, Henry (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Schwarz, Gerard (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Schwartz, Joseph (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Schwartzman, Karen (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - Schwartzman, Seymour (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - Schwender, Margaret (Box 126, Folder 27)
    - Schwender, Peter (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - Sciarpelletti, Giovanni (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - Scott, Kenneth (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - Scott, Mr. Leslie (Box 126, Folder 31)
    - Scott, Richard (Box 126, Folder 32)
    - Scott, Wayne (Box 126, Folder 33)
    - Scovotti, Jeanette (Box 126, Folder 34)
    - Schuller, Gunther (Box 126, Folder 35)
    - Schultz, Sharon (Box 126, Folder 36)
    - Seabold, Nancy (Box 126, Folder 37)
    - Sebury, John (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Seaton, Douglass (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Seattle Opera Association, Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra, Inc. (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Sebastian, Patricia (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Segal, Naomi and Ruth (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Seguin, Shirley Anne (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Seibel, Mary Ann (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Seipt, David (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Sellers, Michael (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Seltzer, Inci Basarir (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Sementovsky, George (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Semon, Gerard (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Sena, Joan (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Senofsky, Berl (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Serbo, Rico (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Sergi, Miss Brasina (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Serkin, David (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Serrlya, Sivia (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Setian, Dorothy (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - Settlement Music School (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Settlement Schools (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Seuffert Band (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Seward, Janice (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Shade, Ellen (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Shadur, Lawrence (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Shaffer, Arthur (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Shakesnider, Wilma (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Shakespeare Festival (New York) (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Shanet, Howard (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Shapey, Ralph (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Shapira, Elijakim (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Shapiro, Alice (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Shapiro, Joel (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Shaprut, Elizabeth (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Sharp, Norma (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Sharp, Robert (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Sharp, Wendy (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Sharpe, John F. (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Shaughnessy, Bernadette (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Shavitz, Carl (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Shaulis, Zola (Ms.) (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Shaw, Karen (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Shear, Nancy J. (Box 128, Folder 24)
    - Sheard, Gayle (Box 128, Folder 25)
    - Shearer, Allen (Box 128, Folder 26)
    - Sheats, Jackson (Box 128, Folder 27)
    - Shell, Audrey Jean (Box 128, Folder 28)
    - Shelton, Kenneth (Box 128, Folder 29)
    - Shepherd, James L. (Box 128, Folder 30)
    - Sherman, Charles H. (Box 128, Folder 31)
    - Sherman, Louise (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Sherr, Frank (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Sherry, Fred (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Shetler, Norman (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Sheveloff, Joel (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Shields, Alice (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Shinall, Vern (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Shindo, Miss Umeko (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Shinn, Phyllis (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Shiran, Ms. Ora (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Shirley, George (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Shores, William (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Shorr, Mara (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Shoshan, Shoshana (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Shriner, Christine (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Shulman, Laurie (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Shuttleworth, Barbara (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Siciliano, Tello (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Siegel, Jeffrey (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Siegling, John (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - Siena, Jerold (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Sigma Alpha Iota Foundation (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Silberberg, Malka (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - Silbiger, Alexander (Box 129, Folder 24)
    - Silliman University (Box 129, Folder 25)
    - Silva-Marin, Guillermo (Box 129, Folder 26)
    - Silverman, Lynne (Box 129, Folder 27)
    - Silverman, Robert (Box 129, Folder 28)
    - Silverman, Sorietta (Box 129, Folder 29)
    - Simeone, Domenico (Box 129, Folder 30)
    - Simeone, Stella (Box 129, Folder 31)
    - Simich, Boris (Box 129, Folder 32)
    - Simmons, Thomas (baritone) (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Simms, Gregory (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Simon, Eric (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Simon, Ilona (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Simon, Joanna (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Simons, Thomas (pianist, composer) (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Simpson, Barbara Ann (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Simpson, Joy (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Simpson, Randolph Linly (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Simpson, Robert (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Simpson, Miss Wallie (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Sims, Diana (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Sims, Gwendolin (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Simuel, Miss Rhomeyn (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Sinclair, Teri Andra (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Singing City (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Sinka, Brenda (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Sisman, Elaine R. (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Sittig, Margaret (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Skarimbas, Elia (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Skoggard, Carl (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Skylight Comic Opera, Ltd. (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Slater-Stone, Arlene (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - Sloat, Karl Thomas (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Slomoff, Lois (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Small, David (Box 130, Folder 26)
    - Smart, Louis Edward (Box 130, Folder 27)
    - Smetona, Anthony A. (Box 130, Folder 28)
    - Smiles, Joan (Box 130, Folder 29)
    - Smiley, George (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Barbara (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Ms. Barrie (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Brian W. (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Carol (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Cary (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Charles Mason (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Christian (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Smith, David (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Donna Turner (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Gayle (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Smith, George Lyndal (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Gladys (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Gregory P. (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Joy Pottle (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Sowiak, Julietta (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Kenneth (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Lawrence (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Smith, Linda Karen (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Smith, Lucille (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Malcolm (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Majorie (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Smith, Maureen (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Smith, Morris L. (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Smith, Muriel Burrell (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Norman (Box 131, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Oliver (Box 131, Folder 27)
    - Smith, Patricia (Box 131, Folder 28)
    - Smith, Phillip (Box 131, Folder 29)
    - Smith, Topper (Box 131, Folder 30)
    - Smith-Meyer, Carolyn (Box 131, Folder 31)
    - Smith, William O. (Box 131, Folder 32)
    - Smithers, Don Le Roy (Box 131, Folder 33)
    - Smithsonian Institution - Division of Musical Instruments (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Snow, Jean (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Snow, Rosemary (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Snyder, Barry Lee (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Snyder, Clifford (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Snyder, Kerala J. (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Snyder, Peter David (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Snyder, Richard (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Sobol, Lawrence (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Society for New Music, Syracuse University (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Society for the Development of Contemporary Brass Music (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Society for the Performing Arts (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Society for the Preservation of the American Musical Heritage (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Society for Strings, Inc. (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Society for Strings, Inc. (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Soffer, Sheldon (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Softus, Anna (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Soho Ensemble, Inc. (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Solari, Mme. Sarah-Fidelia (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - Solum, John (Box 132, Folder 20)
    - Somogi, Judith (Box 132, Folder 21)
    - Sopher, Joseph (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Sorbello, Roberta (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Sorel, Claudette (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Sorenson, Sonja (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Soresi, Dina (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Soskind, Ruth (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Soul Rock from the Rock (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Southeastern Academy of Theatre and Music, Inc. (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Southern Illinois University (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Spaights, James (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Spain, Joan M. (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Spearman, Rawn (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Spears, Jane (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Special Studies (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Spencer, Michael Jon (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Spiegelman, Joel (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Spiller, Joanne (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Spillman, Herdon (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Spillman, Robert and Rosemary (Box 133, Folder 20)
    - Spilsted, Gary (Box 133, Folder 21)
    - Spirit of St. Louis (Box 133, Folder 22)
    - Spivacke, Harold (Box 133, Folder 23)
    - Spotto, Frank H. (Box 133, Folder 24)
    - Spradling, Grant (Box 133, Folder 25)
    - Spriensterbach, Marie Sheldon (Box 133, Folder 26)
    - Spurgeon, Philip (Box 133, Folder 27)
    - Squillacote, Anthony (Box 133, Folder 28)
    - Spring Opera Theatre (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Stafford, James M. (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Stagecraft Corporation (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Stahl, Irwin (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Staiger, Dorothy (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Stakeman, Rudolph (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Stalnaker, William (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Stambaugh, Marilyn (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Stamford, John Scott (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Stamm, Betty (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Stanford, Carolyn (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Stang, Ralph (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Stantz, William (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Stark, Paula (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Starkey, David (Box 134, Folder 15)
    - Starr, Lawrence (Box 134, Folder 16)
    - Staff, Susan (Box 134, Folder 17)
    - State College (PA) Choral Society (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences (Box 134, Folder 19)
    - Statis, James (Box 134, Folder 20)
    - Stawski, Jean (Box 134, Folder 21)
    - Steele, Philip (Box 134, Folder 22)
    - Stefan, Sophia (Box 134, Folder 23)
    - Stein, Gladys (Box 134, Folder 24)
    - Steinberg, Michael (Box 134, Folder 25)
    - Steinbock, Evalyn (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Steiner, Christian (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Steiner, Oliver (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Stem, Carolyn (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Stenborg, Rodney E. (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Stenson, William (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Stephen, John E. (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Stephenson, Anne (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Stephenson, Donna (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Stern, Cheryl (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Stern, Maurice (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Sternbach, David (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Stessin, Herbert (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Stevens, Lorice (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Stevens, Robert (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Stevenson, Alexander (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Stevenson, Delcina (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Stevenson, Edward Bruce (Box 135, Folder 18)
    - Stevenson, Madeline (Box 135, Folder 19)
    - Steward, Pauline (Box 135, Folder 20)
    - Stewart, Dixie (Box 135, Folder 21)
    - Stewart, John H. (Box 135, Folder 22)
    - Stichting International Concerts (Box 135, Folder 23)
    - Stigberg, David (Box 135, Folder 24)
    - Stiles, Dudley Wayne (Box 135, Folder 25)
    - Stillwell, Richard (Box 135, Folder 26)
    - Stivender, Edward (Box 135, Folder 27)
    - Stockinger, Hans D. (Box 135, Folder 28)
    - Stokes, Eleanor (Box 135, Folder 29)
    - Stokes, Nancy (Box 135, Folder 30)
    - Stotlzman, Richard (Box 135, Folder 31)
    - Strahl, Ms. Helmi (Box 135, Folder 32)
    - Stratas, Teresa (Box 135, Folder 33)
    - Stratford Shakespeare Festival (Canada) (Box 135, Folder 34)
    - Straughter, Maralyn (Box 135, Folder 35)
    - Stravinsky Festival - Sacred Service (Box 135, Folder 36)
    - Strebling, Mary Foster (Box 135, Folder 37)
    - Strege, John (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Strickland, William (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - String Apprentice Program (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - String Teachers (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Stringart Quintet (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Striny, Dennis (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Strong, Gail (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Struss, Jane (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Stuart, Avon (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Stuart, James (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Stubblefield, Lionel (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Stull, Susanne (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Styres, Sonia (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Suarez, Richard (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Suburban Opera Company (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Sudock, Shirley (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - Sugita, Tanimichi (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - Sullam, Lucille (Box 136, Folder 18)
    - Sullivan Awards (Box 136, Folder 19)
    - Sullivan, Daniel (Box 136, Folder 20)
    - Suma, Grace (Box 136, Folder 21)
    - Summers, Joan (Box 136, Folder 22)
    - Summers, W. Franklin (Box 136, Folder 23)
    - Summerville, Suzanne (Box 136, Folder 24)
    - Summy-Birchard Company (Box 136, Folder 25)
    - Sun, Evelyn Kuo-Wei (Box 136, Folder 26)
    - Sundquist, David (Box 136, Folder 27)
    - Sunshine, Adrian (Box 136, Folder 28)
    - Surick, Stuart (Box 136, Folder 29)
    - Suskin, Sylvan (Box 136, Folder 30)
    - Sutherland, Rosalie (Box 136, Folder 31)
    - Svendsen, Paul C. (Box 136, Folder 32)
    - Swails, Wesley L. (Box 136, Folder 33)
    - Swanson, Eugene (Box 136, Folder 34)
    - Swathmore College (Box 136, Folder 35)
    - Swem, Andrea (Box 136, Folder 36)
    - Swift, John (Box 136, Folder 37)
    - Swift, Miss Page (Box 136, Folder 38)
    - Symonette, Randolph (Box 136, Folder 39)
    - Symphonic Choral Society of New York, Inc. (Box 136, Folder 40)
    - Symphony for United Nations (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Symphony of Musical Arts (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Symphony Society of Long Island (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Symphony of the Air (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Symphony of the New World, Inc. (Benjamin Steinberg) (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Symphony Society of San Antonio (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Syracuse Symphony Orchestra (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Syracuse University - Edison records archive (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Szabo, Irene (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Szabo, Nancy (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Szaraz, Stephen (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Szigeti, Joseph (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Szilagi, Bela (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Szymanska-Siskind, Janina (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - Taft, Daniel (Box 137, Folder 15)
    - Tagan, Alexsandra (Box 137, Folder 16)
    - Takacs, Peter (Box 137, Folder 17)
    - Takahashi, Yoriko (Box 137, Folder 18)
    - Talaber, Maria (Box 137, Folder 19)
    - Taliaferro, Kerry (Box 137, Folder 20)
    - Talent Bank Foundation (San Francisco) (Box 137, Folder 21)
    - Talley-Schmidt, Eugen (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Tamkin, Stefan (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Tangeman, Nell (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Tanner, Dillard (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Taricani, JoAnn (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Tashjian, Zaven (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Tatum, Nancy (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Taubert, Norma (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Taubman, Martin (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Taylor, Alice Schurman (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Taylor, Betsy (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Taylor, Clifford (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, David (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Taylor, Herman (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Taylor, Richard (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Taylor, Richard F. (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Taylor, Rose (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - Tazaki, Ms. Etsuko (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Teal, Jean-Anne (Box 138, Folder 19)
    - Tecla, Evelyn (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Tedards, Ann (Box 138, Folder 21)
    - Telemann Society (Box 138, Folder 22)
    - Teller, Friedl (Box 138, Folder 23)
    - Teminaka, Henry (Box 138, Folder 24)
    - Temple University (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Tenney, Carol (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Tepfer, Rebecca (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Termine, Robert (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Terry, Alexander (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Terzian, Anita (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Tesoriero, Angela (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Testa, Susan (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Texas Regional Opera Association (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Thamon, Eugene (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Tharp, Robert W. (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Theatre Under the Stars (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Thebom, Blanche (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Thew, Warren (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Theyard, Harry (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Thigpen, Hellen (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Third Street Music School Settlement (Box 139, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, Carlo (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - Thomas, Elijah (Box 139, Folder 19)
    - Thomas, Evan (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Thomas, Fred (Box 139, Folder 21)
    - Thomas, Joel (Box 139, Folder 22)
    - Thomas, Lawrence P. (Box 139, Folder 23)
    - Thomas, Marshall (Box 139, Folder 24)
    - Thomas, Naymond (Box 139, Folder 25)
    - Thomas, Robert (Box 139, Folder 26)
    - Thompson, Arthur (Box 139, Folder 27)
    - Thompson, Ceola (Box 139, Folder 28)
    - Thompson, Darcy (Box 139, Folder 29)
    - Thompson, Elizabeth (Box 139, Folder 30)
    - Thompson, Jan (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Thompson, Kenneth A. (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Thompson, Marcus (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, Leon (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Thompson, Marian (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Thompson, Patti (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Thompson, Shirley (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Thornburgh, Carolee (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Thorne Music Fund, Inc. (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Thornton, Elwood (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Thorsen, Gerald (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Threadgill, Francis (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Tichman and Budevich (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Tick, Judith (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Tippitt, Eric (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - Tirro, Frank Pascale (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - Tisheff, Vera (Box 140, Folder 17)
    - Tobias, Margaret (Box 140, Folder 18)
    - Tocco, James (Box 140, Folder 19)
    - Todd, Carol (Box 140, Folder 20)
    - Toensing, Judith (Box 140, Folder 21)
    - Tofte, Susan (Box 140, Folder 22)
    - Tolkoff, Audrey Lyn (Box 140, Folder 23)
    - Tomaselli, Donato (Box 140, Folder 24)
    - Tomaselli, John (Box 140, Folder 25)
    - Tomere, Jan (Box 140, Folder 26)
    - Tomsic, Dubravka (Box 140, Folder 27)
    - Toolajian, Vahan (Box 140, Folder 28)
    - Toren, Jana and Kristopher (Box 140, Folder 29)
    - Torigi, Richard (Box 140, Folder 30)
    - Torkanowsky, Werner (Box 140, Folder 31)
    - Toscanini Memorial Archive (Box 140, Folder 32)
    - Toscano, Carol (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Tourangeau, Hugette (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Tourigny, Roxana (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Towlen, Gary (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Townsell, Frank (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Townsend, Douglas (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Townsend, Erik (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Tracy, Emily (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Traficante, Marie (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Traverse, Sarah (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Treadway-Carroll, Theresa (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Tree, Michael (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Treger, Charles (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Treigle, Norman (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Treitler, Leo (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Trethaway, Nancy (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Triggan, Beverly (Box 141, Folder 17)
    - Tripp, Alva (Box 141, Folder 18)
    - Tripp, Edward (Box 141, Folder 19)
    - Tritter, Rita Shane (Box 141, Folder 20)
    - Trona, Joan (Box 141, Folder 21)
    - Trott, Laurence (Box 141, Folder 22)
    - Trotter, Linda (Box 141, Folder 23)
    - Troxell, Suzanne (Box 141, Folder 24)
    - Troy, Charles (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Troyanos, Tatiana (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Trussel, Jack (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Tsandikos, George (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Tsilifonis, Lucas (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Tsumura, Miss Mari (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Tulsa Opera (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Tung, Kwong-Kwong (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Turano, Judith (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Turnage, Wayne (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Turnau Opera Association, Inc. (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Turnbull, Walter J. (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Turner, Richard (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Turtle Bay Music School, Inc. (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Tuvelle, Howard (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Twining, Nathan (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Tycho (an Ensemble) (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Tyl, Noel Jan (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Tyler, Veronica (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Tyner, Estelle (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Tynes, Margaret (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Tzincoca, Remus (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Uhlenbroek, Francesca (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Underwood, Kathryn (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Union College, Kentucky (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Universal Symphony Orchestra and Music Institute (UNISOMI) (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - United States - Cultural Presentations Branch (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - United States - Federal Aid to Education (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - United States Information Agency - Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - University of Arizona, Tucson (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - United States - National Endowment for the Arts, National Council for the Arts (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - United States - Office of Education (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - UCLA (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - University of California-Santa Barbara (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - University of Delaware String Quartet (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - University of Georgia (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - University of Minnesota (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - UNLV - Chamber Players (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - University of Southern California (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - University of Washington-Seattle (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - University of Wisconsin - Arts Council (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Unruh, Stan (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Uribe, Blanca (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Utzinger, Lynn Kay (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Uzzo, Louis (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Vaccariello, Lois M. (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Valente, Benita (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Valente, Sallie Coss (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Valentin, Antonio (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Val-Schmidt, Carolyn (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Van Boskirk, Mr. Roe (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Van Buren, Catherine (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Van Ducen, Samuel (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Van Geldern, Harold (Box 145, Folder 16)
    - Van Ginkel, Peter (Box 145, Folder 17)
    - Van Kirk, Mary (Box 145, Folder 18)
    - Van Nes, Bretta (Box 145, Folder 19)
    - Vannin, Teresa (Box 145, Folder 20)
    - Van Tassel, Charles (Box 145, Folder 21)
    - Van Tellingen, Anita (Box 145, Folder 22)
    - Van Way, Nolan (Box 145, Folder 23)